scrabblesolver.net 2017-12-17

# WordSolver | Turn Letters into Words with our scrabble solver!

Log files are maintained (and retained for a few days) and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers. 

Except as stated already, we will make no attempt to identify individual users. You should be aware, however, that access to web pages will generally create log entries in the systems of your ISP or network service provider. These entities may be in a position to identify the client computer equipment used to access a page. Such monitoring would be done by the provider of network services and is beyond our responsibility or control.

We will make no attempt to track or identify individual users, except where there is a reasonable suspicion that unauthorised access to systems is being attempted. In the case of all users, we reserve the right to attempt to identify and track any individual who is reasonably suspected of trying to gain unauthorised access to computer systems or resources operating as part of our web services.

All log file information collected by us is kept secure and no access to raw log files is given to any third party.

This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission.

## Cookies used by this website

Cookies are small computer files that are placed in your browser's storage space in order to remember something between visits - almost all websites use cookies. Please note that cookies can't harm your computer and we don't store any personal information in the cookies we create.

To use this website as it was designed you will need to have cookies enabled on your web browser. Most web browsers have cookies enabled. If you don't want to enable cookies, the basic features of the site should still work. To disable cookies on your browser, please go to [aboutcookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/).

This website uses cookies:

  1. to store your dictionary preference and search-type so that it is remembered the next time you return to this website.
  2. in order to collect anonymous analytics statistics (so we can see which pages are most popular, for instance).
  3. for social media buttons such as the facebook like ([facebook privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)), google plus one ([google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/policies/)), twitter ([twitter privacy policy](https://twitter.com/privacy)), and add this ([addthis privacy policy](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy) and [opt-out](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out)).
  4. for advertising. We use Google DFP for our advertising, and they have their own [Google Advertising Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/policies/privacy/ads/) and [opt-out controls](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb)
